My story.
I've been in the collision business 45 years when I
graduated high school at 17 and I never turned back 45
Years. 45 years.
And I can't wait to retire
and give this to my son.
Yes. So I've got a lot of knowledge in it.
I don't know everything, but I know a lot and I'm a die
and breed in this industry.
Why is that? Why technology has changed everything.
The way they're making the cars now is all about money
for the manufacturers.
And I came from simplicity to extremely difficult.
I'm not geared up for it anymore.
My son is with the computers and the scanning
and the calibration, I'd be lost without 'em.
So that's all required with paint finishes and
Every bit of it, every bit of the repairs are all having
to be done for the manufacturer's specifications.
Without it, there's some big lawsuits,
improper repairs, they'll sue ya. I gotcha.
What is something you think most people don't really
realize about what you guys do?
I don't think they realize the uh, importance
of getting the money we need out of the insurance companies.
It's not a piece of cake. It's hard.
Gotta prove our point on everything.
I follow repair manufacturer's procedures
and that's what help us win the game
with the insurance companies.
So when people are happy with the work that you do,
they don't necessarily understand all the stuff you
had to do in the backend in
Order to, they have no clue.
We try to educate 'em the best we can,
but the whole thing is when they pick the car up from us on
our apron up front, everything we told them
is everything that came true.
Yeah. And they recognize that. Yeah.
You see our Google reviews we're on top.